Ambria Johnson

Contact: (678)613-0298 | 1223ambria@gmail.com | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/ambria-johnson23 | Atlanta, Ga

OBJECTIVE

I am a recent college graduate from Howard University with a projected full-stack web development certificate from the Georgia Institute of Technology. I am a highly motivated individual, looking forward to being in a work environment that encourages innovation and professional growth. With a recent career shift from the healthcare industry to software engineering, I would like to implement a more efficient and user-friendly experience for customers and employees with technology.

EDUCATION

Georgia Institute of Technology | Atlanta, Ga Full Stack Software Engineer Certificate

Howard University | Washington, DC **Bachelor of Science Degree**: Biology

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CVS Pharmacy | Atlanta, GA

Certified Pharmacy Technician

November 2021 - Jan. 2023

- Receiving and storing incoming inventory, verifying quantities against invoices, and checking for outdated medications.
- Performing trouble shooting for clients with insurance issues to resolve problems.
- Maintaining inventory levels, pulling outdated/recalled merchandise.
- Responsible customer service representative; Interacting with customers, receiving and verifying prescriptions and refills.

CVS Pharmacy | Chicago, IL

January 2019 - May 2021

Shift Supervisor (January 2019– May 2021)

- Responsible for assisting the store manager in maintaining a positive work environment, which provides efficient and
 welcoming service guaranteeing a complete quality experience for both the customers and employees.
- Delegated tasks among subordinate employees
- Assisted in employee training and performance management
- Maintained exceptional customer service
- Lead shifts which required completing store tasks and balancing out registers and store safe
- Accountable for recording technical aspects of store sales

Accomplishments:

- Recognized for initiating and finishing responsibilities throughout the store
- Received recognition for remarkable customer service
- Sold 70% above the quota for a CVS rewards program in one day

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

Seattle Cancer Care Alliance | Seattle, Washington

June 2019 – July 2019

Shadowing oncologists specializing in different fields of oncology

Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center | Seattle, Washington

Researcher

June 2018 – August 2019

August 2017 – October 2017

- Quickly learned laboratory skills such as pipetting, aliquoting, gel electrophoresis, and dissociating tissue cells
- Carefully researched with 40 samples of patient DNA for the presence of a particular gene
- Maintained two research projects focusing on Acute Myeloid Leukemia for eight weeks in two principal investigators labs
- Lead college discussions for high school interns at Fred Hutchinson
- Presented research results to established staff

Accomplishments

- Published research data generated from my research results
- Received Human Subjects in Bioethics Completion Certificate

College of Arts and Sciences Graphic Design Internship

Created flyers for events regarding Howard University

Learned basic features of Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator

VOLUNTEER WORK

Howard University Alternative Spring Break

March 2019

- Volunteered in the Washington, DC area focusing on community issues such as homelessness, resources for job opportunities, food deserts, and mental health
- Expanded upon teamwork skills through community service activities
- Volunteered for specific community aspects around the Washington, DC area
- Raised

Executive board member/PR & graphic designer

- Used my Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator skills to create the organizations logo and to create flyers for events
- Created and organized a daily planner for the organization's social media posts on Instagram and twitter platforms
- Co-managed with executive board members for future volunteer work and events

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- APIs
- Nodejs
- SQL
- MongoDB
- Insomnia
- Express
- Visual Studio Code